

# **CONTACT**

Phone: +48 664 770 449
E-mail: d.kuriata88@gmail.com
LinkedIn: /in/dariusz-kuriata
GitHub: /dariuszkuriata

## LANGUAGES

- English C2, German A1
- HTML, XPath, CSS (Selectors)
- SQL

## **TOOLS**

- Jira, Zephyr
- MS SQL Studio, SoapUI
- Git, GitHub
- Visual Studio Code
- IntelliJ, Android Studio

## **SOFT SKILLS**

- Scrupulousness and determination
- Analytical and critical thinking
- Fast learning and adapting to change
- Agile development process and SCRUM

I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment processes pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation).

# **Dariusz Kuriata**

I became a tester after a small revolution in my life. After many years as a teacher I've decided to start learning something new and passed the international ISTQB FL exam. Additionally, I've learned the basics of automated testing with Selenium WebDriver (Java). In my free time I improve my responsive website. I am committed to self-development and open to acquiring new skills.

# **COURSES AND CERTIFICATES**

- ISTQB Foundation Level Certificate
- · Sql for Testers Certificate
- Selenium Essential Training Certificate
- Teaching qualifications (nominated teacher)
- 1st degree School Tutor training course with a certificate

## **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

#### Junior Tester at Soflab Technology Sp. z o.o.

June 2021 - now

- · Preparing test cases for banking applications
- · Conducting e.g. functional and regression tests
- Issue reporting in Jira, working in a Scrum team
- Using SQL databases and SoapUI for testing purposes

## Cooling Services Assistant at Czesław Biliński Refrigeration Systems Repair and Service

September 2019 - February 2021

• Industrial controllers and BMS installation and service

### **English Teacher at EKOLA School Complex in Wroclaw**

September 2018 - August 2019

- Preparing and conducting English lessons in a private primary school
- Promotion: nominated teacher

## English Teacher at Primary and Secondary School in Malczyce

September 2013 - August 2018

- Preparing and conducting English lessons in a public primary and secondary school
- Promotion: contract teacher, Success: Head Teacher's award

## **English Lecturer at ATUT Education Centre in Wroclaw**

November 2010 - June 2013

- Preparing and conducting English lessons in preschools
- Success: Acquiring clients for the company due to a contract with a new preschool

# **EDUCATION**

Master: English Philology translation studies: Corpus linguistic Philological School of Higher Education in Wroclaw

October 2009 - June 2011

Bachelor: English studies and teaching methodology
University of Wroclaw, Foreign Language Teacher Training College

October 2006 - June 2009